question_data = [
	{
		"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
		"type": "boolean",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"question": "In the 1988 film Akira, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.",
		"correct_answer": "True",
		"incorrect_answers": ["False"]
	},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
	 "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash&#039;s starting Pok&eacute;mon in the pilot episode of the cartoon.",
	 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
	 "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
	 "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
	 "question": "The anime Attack on Titan was directed by Tetsur\u014d Araki, the same person who directed the anime Highschool of the Dead.",
	 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
	 "question": "Throughout the entirety of &quot;Dragon Ball Z&quot;, Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
	 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
	 "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False",
	 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
	 "question": "In &quot;To Love-Ru: Darkness&quot;, Yami reveals her real name is Eve.",
	 "correct_answer": "True",
	 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
	 "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.",
	 "correct_answer": "True",
	 "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
	 "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False",
	 "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
	{"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
	 "question": "In Full Metal Panic!, Whispered are those who are capable of creating Black Technology.",
	 "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
